Bye.
The ache is deeper now, a steady beat Stuck to
this vinyl, sticky seat The endless plains of
brown and grey Another piece of me slips away The
world outside is vast and dead Matches the
silence in my head My body's screaming needs a
sign Somewhere on the side of the whole line Are
you my lover? Or are you my guard? Is this a
journey or a prison yard? There's a lock on the
door, a bar on the sky And I'm starting to see the
truth behind the lie A different kind of chill
inside my soul
of
all control
You hold the wallet, you hold the key To every
single heart of me I see you watching from your
seat Your victory feels so complete This wasn't
an adventure, not a game You just needed someone
else to blame A trophy for your bitter prize
Reflected in your empty eyes Are you my lover?
Are you my God? Is this a journey or a prison?
Yeah, there's a lock on the door, a bar on the sky
And I'm starting to see the truth behind the lie A
different kind of chill inside my soul A
creeping loss of all control I can't find my way
back home I can't find my way back home
you.
Are you my God? Is this a journey or a prison yard?
There's a lock on the door, a bar on the sky And I'm
starting to see the truth behind the lie A
different kind of chill inside my soul A
creeping loss of all control
Oh, yeah.